[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "According to the movie Friday the 13th, what year was Camp Crystal Lake established?", "correct_answer": "1935", "incorrect_answers": ["1957", "1979", "1942"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the measure for hotness of a chili pepper?", "correct_answer": "Scoville scale", "incorrect_answers": ["Piquanat scale", "Heat Factor Index", "Scottsdale scale"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who developed a punch card that was used with mechanical tabulating machines in the 1890 U.S. Census?", "correct_answer": "Dr. Herman Hollerith", "incorrect_answers": ["John Napier", "Joseph Marie Jacquards", "Blaise Pascal"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Onco, coming from the Greek word onkos refers to what?", "correct_answer": "Tumor", "incorrect_answers": ["Ear", "Nerve", "Eye"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The amethyst is the symbol and birthstone of this month.", "correct_answer": "February", "incorrect_answers": ["September", "April", "July"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In  April 28, 2001, this famous American multimillionaire became the first space tourist.", "correct_answer": "Dennis Tito", "incorrect_answers": ["Mark Shuttleworth", "Charles Simonyi", "Gregory Olsen"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What legendary actress played Holly Golightly in the 1961 movie Breakfast at Tiffanys?", "correct_answer": "Audrey Hepburn", "incorrect_answers": ["Grace Kelly", "Ginger Rogers", "Marilyn Monroe"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Unlike most sharks, the tiger shark does not grow a replacement tooth every time one is lost.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The movie Red Dawn is set in the city of Calumet, which is located in what U.S. state?", "correct_answer": "Colorado", "incorrect_answers": ["Wyoming", "Utah", "Montana"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What did Erik Rotheim invent in 1926?", "correct_answer": "The aerosol spray can", "incorrect_answers": ["saccharin", "The autopilot", "chewing gum"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many hearts does a typical earthworm have?", "correct_answer": "10", "incorrect_answers": ["2", "4", "8"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the casino version of Blackjack, what is a \u201cshoe\u201d?", "correct_answer": "The container from which cards are dealt", "incorrect_answers": ["The edge of the playing table", "The container where the player puts the cards he/she receives", "The shape of the playing table"]}]